Hello, welcome to the first episode of Learn German in Hindi.
I am Kedar
Jadhav. I live in Germany and
I am a design engineer in the alternative industry,
but my real passion is
teaching German. I completed the institute's CITU, which is the toughest and
highest level certification in the German language,
and for the last four years I have been
teaching German free of cost. During this period,
I have taught German to more than 1100 students out of 4450,
and
many of them have got
hundred percent marks in various exams of the institute. Come on,
my
first and most important reason behind starting this channel is that whoever has a
desire to learn German should get it for
free.
This is my aim.
Nowadays, there are
many opportunities available for those who know the German language well,
but unfortunately,
learning German is not that easy in India. The
fees of good classes are thousands of rupees for every level
and there are not many opportunities in total.
Secondly, when we learn German, we
learn it through English and because of this, many
Students face difficulty and to be honest there are a
lot of similarities between Hindi
and my ...  It also happens like
in English we have read your character
jaguar character, when you say it then you know it is
closed but when you say young students
then you come to know from the context that there are many so once
it was one character and once
it was many characters, as you
go ahead you will understand it happens
in Hindi also, right I will come tomorrow
so you understand that tomorrow is less tumor and I
came tomorrow so you can understand that tomorrow this star,
both these indicators are tomorrow peer everyone, so also
means CBI and also see the meaning and
now I am going to show you immediately that
it is not in English but it is definitely the
same in Hindi, that is ah Deol in Hindi
say you and ah from here that which is also
in German is a capital G capitals in ah
you, I will do it again
in English so it will be
easy for you if you do this you do
not need to remember the right now, it is just going to be put
forward to us, that is why we are doing
this challenge ka yeh Ishq hi how are you
voice mail Jamshed's back Virya  There was a war,
war, you all ji, small ji, give the ball and
capital does not mean, from here this is most important for you, so
think calmly about its simple, very simple, so
how do we set it up in Hindi, so what are some of the things that we do in Hindi,
if this was not for running around, then what do we do, so what do
we do with insurance, we leave some things, we leave some things
and customers
come and peel and then when you have to say
I drink hybrid, then what do I do,
I drink, don't think about it,
I drink, you drink,
he drinks, this is the
thought, you drink, he drinks,
this is called congestion,
what is the important thing in this, once you have
decided that you are betting, then I will place
every bet, if I have to eat, then I eat
food, if it is on, then I know, if I have to come, then I will come till
today, this is
called class condition, so
what did you do, every Hindi, otherwise I was indoors
eating and drinking  Aana-jaana we
removed na and made a mixed team pee and then we used I pee,
you pee, we pee.
If you have clear the basic Hindi work
for education then you will learn German
in 2 minutes how is it the same in German, let's
see
that in German also in every section there is 990
admit this who lift deep go lehman learn
addition food triangle drink if see
everything and myth same work then we will do it like in Hindi
so we had held pee here let's
hold the screen here it came that
wrinkle amit ringtone so what will be its steam
in Hindi, naari,
remove it here that at that time it became tring
tring junun in Hindi it was peewan here it became
trick now what will you do in Hindi remember what you did in Hindi
I am a dog I
applied I pee, come here you will apply this that
if you have said I pee then you will
say this trick which is your slim and if I
apply it then it will be that one of its
creams gets removed but for now let us
remember that we have applied pee, we will say
this  Free from the grip of love, in Hindi if I am there then I
apply it, similarly in German
Ishq will only apply, anytime we will come to that
if he is away then he is in Germany for many days
what did you do you drink here we will
apply juice this team
that you drink or why does he drink Dhoop
Trisandhyam were recent that if there is only
digit if there is only back then we will
apply TVS
that he drinks egg tring tring
clear if both of you are behind then
you both will say he will also apply TVS will
also have ear so let's see Vitti
Niwas if if you are away then apply if you are
active allergy then apply tips
and if it is clear then also apply yellow now
after this I like it very much if you want to say semen
means we or C means will or capital G in all
three cases in this we will not apply again
means we took it out also or put it in so
semen nikal ji wrinkle capital win
wrinkles every cutting will have to be done it is simple we
drink are better people
that they drink Vichitra uncle and you drink
green then every pick again equity
investment so what happened  Iodine of this train, the
second you did everything,
research bearing in the wedding and will make it
different, very simple, so by chanting this,
our minister becomes that mantra, if you
chant it with me, then you will also easily get this mantra, then the
juice of this cream is done by you, print
that this train wear prince which is easy twinkle
simple rate, now after using this you will feel so much,
now how is German, this youth, it is a
European language, so look at all the Indian
languages, there are many, what is it in them,
it always comes at the end, I
play cricket, I play cricket, so in this, it is
worker at the end, similarly in European languages, it is
in the second position, like
in English, it is print sesame, that
I drink, that I also learn penis vitamins,
in Spanish, it is your web
portal, your vote, and similarly,
in German also, it is in the second position,
then and all the rest which is in English,
what will be in the back message one, what is it called,
this and what is it
called drink, after drinking this, it will be put
in the printer, what is it called, this
love thorny, so what do we all do, that
Pepsi also  Let's say that
Rahu's personality is on the child, we do
n't need to learn German, so I drink Pepsi,
this cream Pepsi uterine tipsy, it will taste
tasty,
whatever trick Pepsi video Trikand, that
people drink Pepsi, print it and
eat pizza like this, let's have a side
pizza and speed together or what do we do,
why let's play cricket right now,
okay cricket, how about playing
cricket tomorrow, so let's say TV
is its origin, so what will be made of PPO, this
cleverness is away, so ST I click pillar
cricket, you play cricket by doing another piece,
replay cricket test cricket,
what wave wave wave wave,
you do everything in simple Hindi, after this, as if
we have caught it in Hindi, do
not remove it in it and I am a parrot, you are then it is decided, if you want to
drink ghee simply then I am bad,
I am finished, in German also catch the same pollution,
remove PM, make a stem, if this is there, then
put this stay, so
this is simple, how am I right now
In every language there are some people or
some things which do not follow the rules
which are called Gular but in this
also there are some viruses which do not believe in this
but as we move forward then we will
learn new more than ninety percent of
German words follow this rule so what we will do is
we will learn this regularly and
whatever we see now we will keep moving in this direction it
is clear to everyone right
now I am giving you
this trick you all must be
seeing thirty words on the screen this is the
most important thirty work in your day to day life
like
knowing how to come, layer not to read singhana trim option
how successful you are in making sentences every day from this I have said this
four times till date I have taught you this
roti papad four times you will say this every time
whoever carefully
makes a sentence will get 501 in 3 months the
important thing right now is roles
consistency is important then as we move
forward we will make these sentences complex
but only you  Take a notebook and keep
writing five sentences everyday. Is it done now?
How are you now? What is your problem now?
What is the medium? We can solve the
agency flight problem for 10 minutes. Sir, you
daddy pronouns come and wheat gets it.
So what will you do now? Those who do
n't know white, there is no problem in English also. I want to go
to office. This is deep to all these. I come from
office. From
someone, for us to write in English.
When you have learnt your tour from
here, what is important for you is
make five sentences everyday. There are so many sentences
that even fine words do not fit in them. I
can tell you so many such sandwiches
that you can do it directly in
German. You can do this. Speaks of a
hundred percent of German centers. This is everything.
Print a hundred percent of this. So what
you have to do is like I said about that
cream also, if you want, pause it
and write that 30 words in your notebook
and then make sentences next to it everyday.
Now I want to improve my speaking skills in every class.  Dino
Ponting said Tinder time, it is better that
we can proceed further in this class,
okay, so what you have to do is, as
I said, catch it and remove it,
do it carefully, such that the trap is made, it is clear now, as I said, make simple sentences, I will tell you with some examples, what we do hundred percent is Gurjar one sentence, listen carefully, learn Hindi, do this loop Hindi
mirror, you liquid spilled over
cricket team sprint, it is clear to everyone, in the same way
we can make it, as long as that
Veerval Hindi previous cricket BSP learn cricket, as
long as you are new, make this and view from
because it is easy and it is easy for the brain,
as you grow, keep making sentences near Ash and Beer for two, three, four days, as you
go forward, you will keep making two addresses, at the same time,
you will learn the next concept, then
it will become easier for you, so
now it is clear to everyone, everybody knows how to make small sentences,
see these sentences,
we have learned to make small German sentences in just 10 minutes,
now everyone has understood  Have confidence that you can
make small German sentences,
everyone will make 5 sentences in German every day,
it is simple, isn't it, in this way we will keep learning
new concepts in German by taking the help of Hindi content,
already I have
uploaded nine videos, product nine
videos will come, you will find the link of that in the description of
this video, similarly I will keep
uploading new videos every week, so that is why
this is my request to all of you that
you subscribe to my channel, like it
and
share it with your friends who want to learn German,
and if you have any doubt, if you have
any problem in this, then
write in the comment section, I
will try my best to solve it,
we will definitely learn in the next part, if you get the result, then see you
in the next part,
learn German in Hindi, thank you